

o DETAILS o

+353 879366009 BrianLynch182@gmail.com

o IINKS o

TCDexams.com

Github - BrianLunch

LinkedIn

o OUALIFICATIONS o

Illinois BASSET Cert Food Handler Training Cert FCDL - Microsft Office Cert

o SKILLS o

Java

Prolog

С

Arm Assembly

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Github Proficiency

Haskell

Analytical Thinking

Collaboration & Teamwork

Computer Hardware Knowledge

ReactJS Microsoft Azure

AWS

ECDL - European Computing Driver License

Cloud Computing

Direct Sales Heavy Lifting

Health & Safety

o HOBBIES o

I play football for Trinitys Collegiate team in Irelands top college division

I also play Gaelic football for my local team

I am also a member of Trinitys Computer Science society, DUCSS and enjoy attending their events.

• REFERENCES •

Damien Foley

Head of Cloud Centre of Excellence

Damien.Foley@zurich.com +353 (0) 1 799 2894

Eamonn O'Hare

Company Owner

Eamonn@outdoor.ie +353 (0)1 2960212

BRIAN LYNCH

PROFILE

I am an Irish student from Dublin. I have a J1 VISA and am eligible to work and live in the USA for 4 months. I have experience working in sales and in a large multinational insurance company. I have a 3.85 GPA in this college year and can work flexible hours.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

PROGRAMMING TEACHING ASSISTANT - JAVA at Trinity College Dublin, Dublin, Ireland.

January 2020 - Present

- Assist with a college module which involves creating a Java application in teams of 6 people.
- This position was assigned to me based on my current grades (GPA).
- Graded first year computer science students programming projects weekly.
- Supported them in their learning of the Java.
- Resolved issues that may arise in their group.

CLOUD COMPUTING INTERN at Zurich Insurance Plc, Dublin

May 2019 - September 2019

- Worked as part of a large global team.
- Attended weekly meetings and updated coworkers on my progress and new ideas.
- Built, maintained, patched and logged all servers in Zurich's private cloud.
- Supported clients on any issues via email and calls.
- Helped team members with Azure and AWS tasks.

DISTRIBUTION CO-ORDINATOR at The Outdoor Scene, Kilcoole, Wicklow

May 2018 - September 2018

- Ensured the warehouse met all safety & cleanliness standards.
- Prepared high-end furniture for nationwide delivery.
- Assembled furniture, outdoor heaters and barbecues.
- · Stored new shipments weekly.
- Heavy lifting and transportation of large furniture.
- Completed all relevant paperwork related to the above.

SALESPERSON at The Outdoor Scene, Dublin, Ireland.

February 2020 - February 2020

- Worked the shop floor of a high-end garden furniture store.
- Gained in-depth knowledge about all products sold in the shop.
- Completed sales of furtniture, BBQs and heaters, ensuring complete customer satisfaction.
- Maintained the cleanliness and saftey standards expected.

EDUCATION

Trinity College Dublin, Dublin

September 2017 – Present

Degree: Integrated Computer Science - 3.85 GPA

I have a 3.85 GPA and have completed modules in entrepreneurship, multiple programming languages and mathematics. I have completed presentations in front of hundreds of students and worked hard throughout

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Team Project, Android App Dev

January 2019 - May 2019

• An android app that periodically gather information about nearby Bluetooth devices. I worked on the UI and helped with the use of the bluetooth technology.

Soccer Coach

Summer 2017 - Present

• I voluntarily coached local soccer teams from ages 8-16 for the last 3 years.

TCDexams.com, Website

November 2019 – Present

· Myself and 3 others are developing a website where trinity students can access past exams easier as we found the current website outdated and difficult to use.

Log On and Learn Mentor, Community Initiative

January 2016 - June 2016

 An initiative in my local school which taught older people how to use technology by assigning a mentor to help them over a 5 month period.